<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MobileApplication</string>
    <string name="Activity">If you have worked with C, C++ or Java programming language then you must have seen that your program starts from main() function. Very similar way, Android system initiates its program with in an Activity starting with a call on onCreate() callback method. There is a sequence of callback methods that start up an activity and a sequence of callback methods that tear down an activity as shown in the below Activity life cycle diagram: (image courtesy : android.com )
</string>
    <string name="Fragments">A Fragment represents a behavior or a portion of user interface in a FragmentActivity. You can combine multiple fragments in a single activity to build a multi-pane UI and reuse a fragment in multiple activities. You can think of a fragment as a modular section of an activity, which has its own lifecycle, receives its own input events, and which you can add or remove while the activity is running (sort of like a "sub activity" that you can reuse in different activities).</string>
<string name="Intents">A Fragment represents a behavior or a portion of user interface in a FragmentActivity. You can combine multiple fragments in a single activity to build a multi-pane UI and reuse a fragment in multiple activities. You can think of a fragment as a modular section of an activity, which has its own lifecycle, receives its own input events, and which you can add or remove while the activity is running (sort of like a "sub activity" that you can reuse in different activities).</string>
<string name="Sensors">Most of the android devices have built-in sensors that measure motion, orientation, and various environmental condition. The android platform supports three broad categories of sensors.

Motion Sensors
Environmental sensors
Position sensors
Some of the sensors are hardware based and some are software based sensors. Whatever the sensor is, android allows us to get the raw data from these sensors and use it in our application. For this android provides us with some classes.</string>
</resources>
